

About Me

I was born in 2003 in Iran. I bought my first computer when I was 8 years old. I was very interested in it and did interesting things like photo editing with it. At the age of 14, I became acquainted with programming and felt that this was what I was talented at, so I started learning Android programming only through Google and without a teacher or boot camp. After a while, I developed and published several apps. But after about two years because of more interest in JavaScript I decided to change my stack. I have been working and enjoying Front-End for about two years now.

Contact

2003 Jan 27 Iran, Qom

+98 922 085 2691

AhmadKarimzadeDev@gmail.com github.com/ahmadkzx ahmadkzx.github.io linkedin.com/in/ahmad-karimzade stackoverflow.com/users/13557186 npmjs.com/~ahmadkarimzade

Languages

Persian

in

سروا

Native Langauge

English

Education

High School Diploma, Mathematics Andisheh High School

Ahmad Karimzade

Front-End Developer

Experience

Front-End Developer | 2020/2 - 2020/8 | Qom, Iran | Full Time

AKWeb

Develop About 4 Wordpress Themes

Front-End Developer | 2020/8 - 2021/3 | Tehran, Iran | Full Time

Mizbansite www.mizbansite.com

- Develop Mizbansite main website using Wordpress
- Develop ArtArk website with Vue

Front-End Developer | 2021/5 - 2021/9 | Toronto, Canada | Part Time

Ever Assistant www.everassistant.io

• Debug and improve codes

Front-End Developer | 2020/10 - Present | Qom, Iran | Full Time

Basalam www.basalam.com

- Refactor chat and improve chat speed about 40% by using cache
- Develop about 10 landings for promotions
- · Develop referral games

Professional Skills

HTML & CSS	Javascript	Vue / Nuxt	React / Next
Rresponsive	ES6	SSR	Compontens
Flexbox	Scopes	Vuex	Router
Variables	Asynchronous Js	Routing	Hooks
SEO	Hoisting	Lazy Load	SSR
Standards	Caching	Components	SSG
&	Service Worker	Middleweare	&
Node.js	Type Coercion	Nuxt Helpers	
Rest API Design	Closure	AsyncData / Fetch	
CRUD	Storages	Navigation Guards	
Express	Module Patterns	Transition	
Authentication	&	Plugin	
&		&	

WebVitals Sass Git **Bootstrap PosgreSQL NPM**

Projects

Official

ArtArk (Nuxt)

ArtArk company website, which works in the field of providing SEO services, etc

· www.artark.ir

Maktab Salam (Vue)

Basalam college (Maktab Salam) landing

www.maktab.basalam.com

Mizbansite (Wordpress)

Mizbansite site that provides hosting services

www.mizbansite.com

Vision Team (Vue, Nuxt)

vision marketing team website

www.vizhenteam.ir

iMusicPlus (Wordpress, Vue)

iMusicPlus, download music wordpress theme

· www.imusicplus.ir

GamePlus (Vue, Wordpress, Wocommerce)

GamePlus wordpress gaming shop theme.

www.artark.ir/demo/GamePlus

AKMovie (Wordpress)

AKMovie, download movie wordpress theme

www.artark.ir/demo/AKMovie

Open Source

Personal Blog (React, Next)

My personal blog

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/blog

File Creator VSCode Extension (Node, VSCode)

Create files using templats extension

- www.marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName= AhmadKZX.file-creator
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vscode-file-creator

Trello Clone (Vue)

Trello clone project without API. using Vue and Vuex

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/trello-clone

Vue Router Loading (NPM, Vue)

Easy to use and highly customizable Vue Router Loading

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-router-loading
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-router-loading

Vue Hover Zoom (NPM, Vue)

Easy to use package for zoom image when hover on it with the mouse cursor

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-hover-zoom
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-hover-zoom

H-Chat (React, Node, Socket.io)

Simple realtime chat web app using socket

www.github.com/ahmadkzx/h-chat

Vue Super Console (NPM, Vue)

Beautiful floating console for Vue with features such as screenshot, copy log text and... replace of the browser console.

- www.npmjs.com/package/vue-super-console
- www.github.com/ahmadkzx/vue-super-console